(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC DISTORTS)
(DOOR OPENS)
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (RATTLING)
(MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING OVER TV)
(SIGHS, CONTINUES
MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
WAYMOND: Uh...
(WAYMOND GASPS)
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Oh, I have to finish
all this before...
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Go and steam
the tablecloths for tonight.
I'm going to paint over that
water stain in the ceiling.
(WAYMOND SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(BELL RINGS)
WAYMOND: Huh!
- (EVELYN CHUCKLES)
- (COMPUTER TRILLS)
- Huh? Oh.
- (WATER BUBBLING)
Like, this afternoon?
- Evelyn: Five minutes!
- What?
(WAYMOND SPEAKS MANDARIN)
Which paint did you use?
(EVELYN REPLIES MOCKINGLY)
(CHAIR SCRAPES)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GONG GONG SHOUTS IN CANTONESE)
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Joy is here? Go set the table.
He must be hungry.
(GONG GONG CONTINUES SHOUTING)
- WAYMOND: We talk later?
- (DOOR SHUTS)
(SIGHS)
(EERIE SOMBRE MUSIC PLAYING)
(KISSES NOISILY)
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, hey!
Thank you for doing this.